Guide to the Records of the Research Institute for the Study of Man's (RISM) Study of Chronic Marihuana Users in Jamaica (The Ganja Study) RISM.RG.12
New York University Archives
- Series V: Newspapers and Clippings
  - Articles concerning national and international legal efforts to control drug use, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Appendix
  - Marijuana Revisited: The Health Problem (3 copies), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Marijuana Revisited: The Legal Problem (2 copies), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Effects in Man of Short- and Long-term Use of Cannabis (draft), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Marihuana Problem: An Overview, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Report of Hawaiian Public Health Service re: Medicinal Uses of Marijuana, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Misc. article, The Lancet, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - The Use and Effects of Cannabis, 1970-71 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Chevannes report, Part 1, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - A Report of the National Commission on Ganja, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Claudia Rogers, Alpond report, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Melanie Dreher report, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - The US Journal of Drug and Alcohol Dependence, 1977, 1978, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 12)